Exhibition Records, 1942-2001
Smithsonian Institution Archives
- Claudine Klose, Project Manager, Series 2
  - Box 9
    - SAL - Host scientists interview transcripts, 1993 (Box 9 of 16)
    - SAL - Host scientists interview transcript corrections, 1993 (Box 9 of 16)
    - SAL - Host scientists interview releases, 1993-1994 (Box 9 of 16)
- Steve Schloss, Researcher Graphics Coordinator, Series 3
  - Box 10
    - Notes and outgoing memos, 1990-1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Images list and photo file (Box 10 of 16)
    - Copyright information, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Copyright documents, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Aerosol cans, 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society, 1991-1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Philosophical Society Library, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Science images and notes, 1989 (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Science exhibit images collection (Box 10 of 16)
    - American Type Culture Collection, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Archive Photos, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Argonne National Laboratory, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Arriola, Gus, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - ATT Archives, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Barton, Jacqueline, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Bettmann Archive, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Boston Globe, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 10 of 16)
    - Brooks, Gordon, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Bryan College, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - California Institute of Technology, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Center for the History of Chemistry, 1989 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Charette Corp., 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Chemical Heritage Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Chicago Historical Society, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Coal Miners Music, Inc., 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Cold Spring Harbor Library, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Columbia University, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Cornell University, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - CP-1 Back-up, 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Culver Pictures, Inc., 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - DNA model (Box 10 of 16)
    - Don Wright, Inc., 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower Library, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Eastman Photo, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Fallout shelter, 1991-1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Gannett USA Today, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Geis, Irving, 1989 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Genentech, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - General Electric, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - General Electric, Nuclear Energy, 1991-1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Globe Photos, Inc., 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - GMI Alumni Historical Collection, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - GPU Nuclear Corporation, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Hagley Museum and Library, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Hall of History Foundation, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Hanford Nuclear Reservation, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Hampton University Archives, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Harvard University Archives, 1990-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Herblock Cartoons, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Image, Inc., 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Iowa Department of Economic Development, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - JB Pictures, Ltd., 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - John Hopkins University, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Klipper, Stuart, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Korad Laser, 1985 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Lawrence back-up, 1988-1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Levi Strauss Co., 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Library of Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Los Angeles Times Syndicate, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Macmillan Magazines Ltd., 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Magazines Galore, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Magnum Photos, Inc., 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - May, Ron, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - MIT Museum, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Moorland Springarn Research Center, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Museum of New Mexico Press, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Museum of the City of New York, 1991-1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - National Archives, 1990-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - NASA, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - National Enquirer, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - National Museum of Health and Medicine, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - National Portrait Gallery, 1989 (Box 10 of 16)
    - National Science Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Newsweek, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - New York Botanical Garden Library, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - New York Public Library, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - New York Times, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - New Yorker, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - New Zealand Geographic, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Photo Researchers, Inc., 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Playboy Enterprises, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Robinair Company, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Robinson, Wallace, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Rochester Chronicle and Democrat, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Sagan, Carl, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Scientific American, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Shipping port, 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Smithsonian Archives, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Sophia Smith Collection, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Spilhaus, Athelstan (Box 10 of 16)
    - Stock Montage, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Sunset Publishing, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Superstock, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Syntex Laboratories, Inc., 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Szasz, Suzanne, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Time-Life Books, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Tribune Media Service, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - United Media, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - U.S. Geological Survey, 1993-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - University of California, Irvine, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - University of California, San Francisco, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - University of Michigan, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - W. H. Freeman and Company, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Wide World Photos, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Worchester Foundation, 1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Yale University, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - SAL video index, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Video notes, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Film/Video agreement forms, 1992-1994 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Video clips letters, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Video information - McCarthy and segregation, 1950s, 1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Audiovisual, 1990 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Sputnik - Films, newsreels, 1990 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 3.2.2 - Scopes Trial - Correspondence and memoranda, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 3.4.4 - World's Fair - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 5.2.1 - 50s Living Room - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 5.3 - The Pill - Correspondence and clippings, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 5.6 - Rachel Carson - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 6.1.1 - Science in the Public Eye - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
    - Section 6.2.1.3 - DNA/Cambridge Hearings - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10 of 16)
- Pete Daniel, Curator, and Smita Dutta, Researcher, Series 4
  - Box 11
    - Rachel Carson, 1993-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Rachel Carson - "Silent Spring" video, 1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Rachel Carson - Pesticides Then and Now, 1993-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Correspondence - National Museum of Natural History, 1988 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Home - Albuquerque Museum, 1992-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Home - Princess Jeanne, Home Gardens insert (Box 11 of 16)
    - Home - Princess Jeanne, early stuff, 1992-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Home - Princess Jeanne photographs, c. 1958 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Mickey Mouse Gas Mask, 1990-1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Brier, Jennifer, 1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Forman, Paul, 1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Goldberg, Art and Stan, 1991-1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Heald, Sarah, 1991-1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Hutchins, Louis, 1990-1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Mann, Nick, 1990 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Massie, Sam, 1992-2001 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Researcher's reports, 1990-1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Pete Daniel - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Manhattan Project - Women scientists, 1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Manhattan Project - Personal accounts, 1990-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Badges, Filipkowski, 1991-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Bud Gallagher, atomic cloud sampling, 1992-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Bud Gallagher photographs, 1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Las Vegas, 1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Marshall Islands, 1992-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Nuclear Testing - Paul Zimmer, 1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Radiation - Monitoring equipment, 1991-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Radiation equipment - Dosimeters, etc., 1991-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 - Documents for designer, 1991-1995 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 - Photographs, 1942-1975 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 video drafts - Sound Light, July 1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Chicago Pile - Sound Light, 1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 - Helen Weiss Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Chicago Pile - Jim Chimbidis, 1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 - People Images, 1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - CP-1 - Small scale model, 1991-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Fallout shelter, 1992-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Donation of family fallout shelter, 1990-1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Greater St. Louis Citizens Committee for Nuclear Information - Baby Tooth Survey, 1990-1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Hanford reactor - Images and information, 1991-1992 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Hanford reactor - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Hanford - Shari Van Enkevort, 1992-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Hanford Downwinders Coalition, 1991-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Los Alamos Historical Museum, 1991 (Box 11 of 16)
    - Los Alamos Lab Archives - Badges, 1993-1994 (Box 11 of 16)
  - Box 12
    - Los Alamos - Little Boy, 1989 (3 folders) (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic Veterans - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic Veterans - Sandra Marlow, 1980-1992 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic Veterans - Michael Gramlich, 1992 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic Veterans - Camillo Balsamo, 1991 (2 folders) (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic artifacts - Robert Harris' collection, 1991-1993 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Atomic Bomb - Aftermath photograph research, 1994 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Chemical warfare posters, 1991 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Rhone-Poulenc Ag Company, 1991-1992 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Smita Dutta - Memoranda, 1993-1994 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Miscellaneous records for sections 4 and 5, 1992-1994 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Transmittal of materials - Sarah Heald to Smita Dutta, September 1992 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Templeton, Michael - Consultation in Science Learning, 1990 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Tuskegee Syphilis Study, 1990 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Prairie View A M University - High Energy Physics Group, Dennis Judd, 1992-1995 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Super Conducting Supercollider (SSC), 1992-1994 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Project Plowshare - Peaceful uses of the atom, 1990-1991 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Pesticides - Crop dusters, 1992 (Box 12 of 16)
- Pat Gossel, Curator, Series 5
  - Box 12
    - SAL - Public Response - Pill, 1994-1998 (4 folders) (Box 12 of 16)
    - Advisory Board, 1990-1991 (Box 12 of 16)
    - Ozone hole curriculum kit, 1992-1994 (2 folders) (Box 12 of 16)
  - Box 13
    - Curatorial - Memoranda and notes re. early exhibit ideas, 1989-1990 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Curatorial - Materials distributed, memoranda, and notes re. theme ideas, 1990-1991 (4 folders) (Box 13 of 16)
    - Minds on Science - Videodisc, 1994 (3 folders) (Box 13 of 16)
    - CFC case study - Miscellaneous notes and memoranda, 1991-1994 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Antarctica setting - Exhibits Central, 1992-1993 (Box 13 of 16)
    - NSF Polar Programs, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Deschler, Terry, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Hoffman, David, 1992-1993 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Rowland, F. Sherwood, 1992-1995 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Solomon, Susan, 1992-1994 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center - Section 9, Looking Within, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center - Section 10, Scientist in You, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center - Section 11, Interconnections, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
- David K. Allison, Curator, Series 6
  - Box 13
    - Science themes, 1990-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Blueprints, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Memorandum, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Dorfman figures, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - HVAR 5" rocket, 1992-1993 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Curriculum project, 1993 (Box 13 of 16)
- Elena Tabachnick, Educator, Series 7
  - Box 13
    - Gender, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Ned Heindel comments, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Scientist in You - Floor plans and specs, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Scientist in You - New, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Scientist in You - Old, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Budget, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Looking Within, 1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Memoranda - Science content, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Memoranda, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Interactives - Evaluation, general, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Interactives - Computer, general, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Interactives - Chronology, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Interactives - Hands on Science design, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Interactives - Coal tar, 1991 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Preview area, 1991-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center - Proposals and critiques, 1990-1991 (Box 13 of 16)
- Deborah D. Hilke, Chief Educator, Series 8
  - Box 13
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 13 of 16)
    - Memoranda, 1989-1992 (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 13 of 16)
  - Box 14
    - Memoranda, 1989-1992 (Folder 2-3 of 3) (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL schedules - Education, 1991-1992 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Budget and budget cut records, 1990-1991 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Audience research budget (Box 14 of 16)
    - Theater budget, 1992 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL education, 1992 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Activity checklist (Box 14 of 16)
    - Hands on History Room, 1991 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Chronology section, 1991 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Interconnections, 1991-1992 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Looking Within, 1992 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Scientist in You, 1991-1992 (Box 14 of 16)
- Eleanor Boyne, Project Manager (Post-Opening Phase), Series 9
  - Box 14
    - SAL charter and other documents, 1990-1993 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL press kit, 1994 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, schedules and budget records, 1987-1995 (2 folders) (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL maintenance, 1993-1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL - Wendy Stevens report, 1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL - Post Mortem, 1994-1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Modification of contract - Tom Snyder Productions, 1996 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL Trademark Logo, 1994-1996 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Oxychem fund, 1993-1996 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL Financial Report, 1994 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL security issues, 1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL Joint Review Project, 1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL Punch Lists, 1994 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL/ACS Project - Funding, 1995-1996 (Box 14 of 16)
    - SAL Upgrades/Revisions, 1995-1996 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Chedd-Angier Production contract, 1993 (Box 14 of 16)
    - ACS Contract, 1989, 1995 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Amendment - ACS Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 14 of 16)
    - ACS Invoices, 1990-1993 (Box 14 of 16)
    - Report - "An Assessment of the 'Science in American Life' Exhibition at the National Museum of American History" prepared by Institutional Studies, Smithsonian Institution, 1995 (Box 14 of 16)
- Ann Rossilli, Exhibit Designer, Series 10
  - Box 14
    - Looking Ahead, 1992-1994 (Folders 1-2 of 3) (Box 14 of 16)
  - Box 15
    - Looking Ahead, 1992-1994 (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 3, 1993-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 4 - The Bomb, 1993-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Chicago Pile-1, 1992-1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Nuclear testing, 1993-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Science mobilized, 1993-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 5 - 1950s house, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 5 - The Pill, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 6 - General engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 6 - Antarctica, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 6 - Super Conducting Supercollider, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 6 - CFC's/Ozone, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Section 6 - Three Mile Island, 1992-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Recombinant DNA gene splicing, 1992 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Chronology interactives, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Specifications - Science in American Life exhibit, ODC no. 913016, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Science panels, 1992 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Labels, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Mannequins - Remsen Lab, 1993-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Audio/Video information, 1992-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Office of Design and Construction (ODC) - Review, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Ask Yourself panels, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Host scientist photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Logo, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Graphics and typography, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Punch lists, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Design monthly project reports, 1992-1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Douglas/Gallagher meetings, 1993 (Box 15 of 16)
    - WGBH, 1994 (Box 15 of 16)
    - Miscellaneous memoranda, correspondence, and design records, 1992-1994 (3 folders) (Box 15 of 16)
- American Chemical Society, Series 11
  - Box 16
    - American Chemical Society, March 1987-June 1988 (2 folders) (Box 16 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society, July 1988-1989 (2 folders) (Box 16 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society, 1990-1991 (Box 16 of 16)
    - Agreement with National Museum of American History (NMAH), 1988-1990 (Box 16 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society (Liaison committee), 1991 (Box 16 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society Board of Directors meeting with NMAH, 1988 (Box 16 of 16)
- Administrative Records, Series 12
  - Box 16
    - SAL administration, 1990-1994 (2 folders) (Box 16 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society, 1987-1994 (Box 16 of 16)
    - General correspondence, 1988-1997 (5 folders) (Box 16 of 16)
    - SAL/SI Council meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 16 of 16)
    - SAL host scientist scripts, 1993-1994 (Box 16 of 16)
    - SAL diversity issues, 1992-1993 (Box 16 of 16)
    - SAL fund raising, 1992-1994 (Box 16 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center, 1992-1993 (2 folders) (Box 16 of 16)
    - Main labels, 1994 (Box 16 of 16)
    - Interactives - Chronology, 1992-1993 (Box 16 of 16)
    - SAL Japan show - International Access Corporation, 1995 (Box 16 of 16)
    - Polling station, 1993-1995 (Box 16 of 16)
    - Presentations, 1991-1992 (Box 16 of 16)